Fin
Kunahama High 2nd Year
Kurashina Asuka
Welcome to the All-Japan Flying
Circus Fall Tournament!
We are moments away from the final
of the West Kyushu qualifiers,
which has the Free-Spirited
Flying Fish, Kurashina Asuka,
going up against the Summer
All-Japan Champion, Inui Saki!
Kunahama High 2nd Year
Kurashina Asuka
Kairyou Academy 2nd Year
Inui Saki
Nobody could've predicted Kurashina
making it all the way to the final.
Who knows what this match
has in store for us?
I'll give it my all!
Saki...
I will not stand for another
game like the semifinal.
You must fly with grace
and silence your opponent.
I know.
I'll put on a perfect display of our FC.
An absolutely perfect one.
Let's do this.
Fly!
Let's have a good game, Inui-san.
I couldn't have made it this
far without losing to you.
My weak, no-good self
got plunged into the fires of hell,
and then rose from the ashes.
Like in Zephyrion, you know?
No, I don't.
Figures.
Sorry about that.
This match
won't go anything like the
one against the zipzap girl.
You'd best be ready.
I understand.
I am ready to have a blast.
"Have a blast"?
Yeah.
I mean...
Flying is just so much fun.
You enjoy it too, don't you?
On your marks...
Set!
Episode Twelve:
"Let's... Soar Higher!!"
Here we go. The final is underway.
Both players are start off
using low yo-yos to speed up.
Inui, a speeder, has pulled ahead!
Damn, she's quick.
She overtook Asuka-senpai!
Inui-san really is quick.
Don't hold back, Asuka.
Push the pedal to the metal
right from the get-go!
Got it!
Whoa! Three straight Sonic Boosts!
She's being awfully aggressive
this early in the game.
Saki. Shortcut.
Okay.
Point to Kurashina! 1-0!
For the first time this tournament, Inui
has lost the race to the second buoy!
I have the upper hand now!
This takes the Birdcage out of the picture!
That's so like Kurashina-kun.
Asuka! Keep going and slip past her!
No, you won't.
Is that...
There it is!
Pentagram Force!
Oh, my! Her maneuvers are drawing
a five-pointed star in the sky!
It's a pentagram!
She modified the Delta Force?
Pentagram... Force...
What an awesome name!
That's what you noticed?
Way to go in guns blazing, Asuka.
She practiced this a whole lot!
Inui-san stopped!
This move...
I came up with it so I could
face you on equal footing.
Saki...
If we figure out the pattern,
we can predict where she'll go.
Stay calm.
Okay, Irina.
Behind you.
Now we're tie—
Point to Kurashina! 2-0!
That's it, Kurashina! That's the spirit!
Use the recoil to take the third buoy.
Okay.
Kurashina has amazingly taken
a two-point lead over Inui!
But Inui instantly made a
beeline for the next buoy!
They didn't dwell on it at all. Impressive.
Take a shortcut to the third line!
Got it!
Point to Inui! 2-1!
Okay, Saki.
Get your payback on the third line.
Okay.
It's my turn now.
Above you!
She's evading all her attacks by a whisker!
Yeah.
It's not like the last time I played her.
She's enjoying this?
W-Wow...
All that practice is paying off.
Those three-on-one drills
helped prepare her for this.
Inui's unleashing a barrage of attacks,
but Kurashina's dodging all of them!
That's the way, Asuka!
Stay alert!
I know!
Misaki-chan.
Mashiro-chan.
Madoka-chan.
Captain.
Rika-chan.
Satouin-san.
Shindou-san.
And Kagami-sensei...
And Coach!
She evaded every last one...
Above you, Saki!
I'm going to hit her with all
the hopes you entrusted to me!
Hyper...
Low Yo-Yo!
Point to Kurashina! 3-1!
She scored! That's Kurashina's third point!
Nailed it!
There are three minutes left in the game.
Three minutes is all that stands
between Asuka and victory!
Saki.
Turn off your balancer.
Okay.
Phase first...
Fifty percent unl—
No.
One-hundred percent unlock.
Got it.
Inui-san?
Agravain...
Phase second...
What the hell is that?
Complete balancer
unlock.
Inui-san...
It is time for silence to descend upon us!
She tweaked the balancer on her Grav-Shoes?!
No...
She cut it off completely!
Can you even do that in-flight?
Avalon!
They entered the market only a few years ago,
but they've already developed
that kind of technology?
What's going on?
Turning off the balancer,
which acts as a safety device,
would make you unable to maintain
your balance in mid-air.
But control your Grav-Shoes in that state,
and you'll be able to use them
to their fullest capability.
I can't believe it's possible
to control them that perfectly.
She must have extraordinary
stamina and reflexes.
Asuka!
Use Sonic Boost to put
some daylight between you!
And then go for the buoy!
Okay!
Not on my watch.
Point to Inui!
Point to Inui! 3-3!
Now we're tied.
That's enough, Saki.
Proceed to Greensleeves.
Show them how beautiful you can be.
Th-This is...
What in the world is that move?
Asuka...
Do something, anything to get free!
Resistance is futile.
That's the perfect closed world
we created together with Avalon.
Listen to the pin-drop silence that
has befallen the entire venue.
This is Avalon's symphony!
Time's up!
T-Time has run out!
Since the match has ended in a 3-3 draw,
we will now have a ten-minute break,
and then extra time!
Extra time after a draw in regulation...
The finale to our FC is upon us.
A chance like this does
not come around often,
so we arranged a little
curtain call of sorts.
Five minutes in which we toy
with our powerless opponent.
Five minutes of perfect silence and beauty.
Asuka!
Asuka-senpai!
Asuka-chan!
What's wrong, Brother?
Those "Agravain" Grav-Shoes...
Their balancer parameters can be
freely tweaked during a match, huh?
And then we have Inui-kun, who
has the ability to control
those Grav-Shoes at will.
Oh, Shindou-kun.
So even the King of Kings doesn't
have a solution to this problem?
Yes, for now.
As much as I hate to admit it.
But Kurashina-san...
I think Kurashina-san is amazing, too.
Kurashina-kun?
Yeah.
We still don't know the
limits of her ability.
She might still have major
potential hidden away.
Yeah.
She might show us something
even more entertaining.
Marvelous.
You are all right, yes?
Things don't look all right over there, though.
She doesn't seem likely to last
the five minutes of extra time.
Just a bit more...
I wish I could've flown
with her just a bit more.
With Kurashina Asuka.
Saki?
Asuka.
Do you have any HP left, Asuka-senpai?
Amazing.
It's incredible she can fly so freely
after turning off her balancer.
Inui-san keeps soaring ever higher.
This match is so much fun!
Asuka...
Coach.
What is it?
I want to turn off my balancer, too.
That's reckless!
Don't you remember how you couldn't fly
at all the last time you tried that?
Yeah!
Besides, your Grav-Shoes
aren't like Avalon's.
You can't calibrate them mid-flight.
Once you turn the balancer
off, there's no going back.
Do you still want to?
I don't want this to be the end!
I want to keep flying with Inui-san!
Please let me, Coach!
I don't care if I get burned to ashes!
We care!
You're not Zephyrion, you know.
But...
She might just become the
Master of the Heavens.
Not you too, Misaki-senpai!
Let's trust Asuka on this, Masaya.
I'm sure she'll be fine.
Got it.
I'll leave everything to Asuka.
I will, too!
I'm counting on you, Asuka.
M-Me, too!
Okay!
Me three, Kurashina!
Got it!
Did you feel it?
Our FC, and the perfect
silence it brings about?
It was the same back then.
Accompanying the beautiful
spectacle you put on
was a deafening silence in the air.
That was just fear.
Two athletes putting their skills to
the test, competing against each other,
and bringing joy to both the
players and the audience...
That's what the sport of
Flying Circus is all about.
If it were simply about overwhelming
one's opponent to win,
its name wouldn't include the word "Circus."
I can't wait to see whether you can say
the same thing after extra time ends.
The extra time period in the
final will begin shortly.
Here we go.
This is the first time in this tournament
that a match has gone into extra time.
Extra time will last five minutes.
If a winner isn't decided within
that time, we'll go to sudden death!
You didn't run away, eh?
I applaud your courage.
Inui-san.
I'll fly with you all the
way this time, for sure.
On your marks!
Set!
Asuka!
She doesn't even have the energy
to fly straight anymore.
No.
Two silhouettes soared through the skies
Her Grav-Shoes' wings...
Don't tell me you turned off...
Spreading the wings on their backs wide
...the balancer, yes.
So I could fly with you.
What?
There's no way you can stay in control!
Here I go.
Go!
Point to Kurashina!
She actually has her shoes under control?
Unbelievable.
Go straight for the third buoy!
Got it!
Mind-boggling. There's no
other way to describe this.
Saki! Go after her right now!
Okay!
Thinking about it won't get me anywhere
I know it can't go on like this
Take a shortcut, Saki!
Okay!
Point to Kurashina! 5-3!
Holy cow! This is beyond unbelievable!
Does having more obstacles make one
In a matter of seconds, Kurashina
got her Grav-Shoes under control
Strive even harder? Round and Dream
and took a two-point lead over Inui!
You can do this, Asuka!
Let's race
You're amazing!
This has turned into one crazy match.
It really has.
To the vapor trail
With this, the sport of
FC will evolve once again.
Players will be freed from
the shackles of balancers.
Beyond the blue
You soared through the skies
with a smile on your face
It's the dawn of a new era.
Now, Saki!
That's all I need to fly
higher and farther than ever
Use Greensleeves again to pin her down!
Saki?
The summer breeze
What's the matter?
Carries the scent of the sea
and all your voices to me
What's this feeling?
It's the same as back then.
And gives me the wings
of courage I need to fly
It feels like my body's burning up again.
Inui-san!
Let's have a blast.
"Have a blast"?
I don't know how.
Let me show you how, then!
Your softly spoken words
And your fleeting gaze
Point to Inui!
Make me want more
5-4!
Saki?
Please keep your eyes on me
Inui-san's expression changed?
She seems full of life!
Let's fight
Point to Kurashina!
6-4!
Asuka-chan seems to be having so much fun.
Yeah.
Wearing our hearts on our sleeves
Inui-san...
Let's soar even higher...
Beyond the blue
Together!
You soar through the skies
with a smile on your face
Yeah.
That's all I need to fly
higher and farther today
I've never seen Saki beaming
like that during a match before.
As a new day dawns upon us
Point to Inui!
6-5!
Show me once again
The wings of courage I need to fly
Point to Inui!
6-6!
We're all tied up!
Not long left to go now in extra time!
What is that?
Coming to a standstill
I...
So pretty.
Yeah.
How dazzling.
I see above me a sky so high
Yeah. I can't take my eyes off it.
Their contrails...
If we can't go it alone
How...
How very unsightly.
Let's go together
They're merely chasing
after each other endlessly
and competing to see who's better.
Wings on the sky
But still...
It's so,
You soared through the skies
with a smile on your face
so very beautiful.
Th-This sight is beyond
anyone's wildest imagination,
That's all I need to fly
higher and farther than ever
so I hope you'll forgive me
for being speechless there,
but the five minutes of extra
time have already passed!
The summer breeze
Now, whoever scores the next point wins!
Carries the scent of the sea
and all your voices to me
And gives me the wings...
She lost control?!
Inui's gonna touch her back!
Was it no good after all?
No good?
No...
It's not!
P-Point to Kurashina!
Kurashina wins, 7-6!
Misaki-chan?
What's wrong with you? You went and won!
Congratulations, champion!
Champion...
Thank you so—
Kurashina!
Thank you for fulfilling my dream!
You're crying too much, Bro.
You won, huh?
Yeah,
we won.
But, more importantly,
it was so much fun!
I concede.
All these years, I've wanted your
approval because I admired you.
But perhaps I went about it the wrong way.
That's not true.
I always thought I'd made a huge mistake.
But now that I know it played a big
part in broadening FC's horizons,
a weight's been lifted off my shoulders.
I think I understand the significance
of the word "Circus" a little now.
Flying Circus is a fun sport that brings
joy to people's hearts, isn't it?
Did you have fun?
I sure did.
As much as I hate to admit it.